number six then you know how do you know
you're a special person okay like
meditation number six how do you know
you're a special person because you know
the diamond cutter Sutra or you know the
Heart Sutra you met it in your lifetime
okay
you met the diamond cutter Sutra
Shinkansen
you met hinging in your life okay then
you must be amazing you must be special
okay because you made it you made the
diamond cutter Sutra you made the Heart
Sutra you know you can't go home ever
again and say I'm not very good person
I'm not very special person you know I'm
always sad and unsure of myself I have
anxiety all the time okay that's true
but you're also special because you met
you created the Buddhism on this planet
you created G Khun Jane you credit
Shinji
you created DCI you created gun mountain
it's all come from you okay so have a
little appreciation for yourself okay
that's meditation number six the fruits
of a visit which is the name of
meditation number six it means we don't
live in a time when we can meet the
historical Buddha Gautama Buddha left as
well okay but we can enjoy the fruits of
his visit okay we we have the Heart
Sutra
we have the diamond cutter Sutra we have
a tradition which has not been broken
for two and a half thousand years okay
y'all go to the gala you do know your
mug
to another the patient to wonder
something get used to that we every two
weeks we recite the lineage you are part
of an unbroken lineage okay that the
teachers are there it's never been
broken you are part of it you're the
next link in an unbroken chain since
Buddha okay then be a little happy about
yourself okay and the fruits of a visit
means that the fact that you have the
Heart Sutra the fact that you have the
diamond cutter Sutra in your world is
the is the fruits of Lord Buddha coming
here okay on it so proof that we are
blessed so these two meditations
meditation number five where you
understand you are the Sangha jewel the
meditation number six where you
understand you had enough karma to live
in a world where Buddhism is still alive
these two meditations are supposed to
make you happy about yourself and your
life okay so if you do these two
meditations well when you get up out of
that meditation you should like Swagger
a little bit like um oh cool yeah you
know you should be a little happy about
your life okay because only one creature
in a billion can have the Heart Sutra or
diamond cutter suit okay you're special
you are special you are extremely rare
in the universe okay
you are at the top of the food chain
Dharma food chain you're up here you
know you have all these teachings you
have the Pens
you have the four steps okay you you're
extraordinarily special in the universe
you are the most special people universe
you got a if you succeed at meditation
number five and number six you should
come out of your
you know get up make lunch like you know
I'm pretty cool actually
okay you should feel happy okay